Student Newspapers; Collection ua809
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Albany Student Press, 1990s, 1990-1993; 9
  - Albany Student Press, 1991; 2
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 8, 1991 February 26
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 9, 1991 March 5
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 10, 1991 March 8
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 8, 1991 March 12
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 12, 1991 March 15
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 11, 1991 March 19
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 13, 1991 April 5
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 14, 1991 April 9
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Student Association Elections Endorsement Supplement, 1991 April 12
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 15, 1991 April 12
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 16, 1991 April 16
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 17, 1991 April 19
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 19, 1991 April 23
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 19, 1991 April 26
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 20, 1991 April 30
    - Aspects, 1991 May 3
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 21, 1991 May 3
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 21, Summer Issue, 1991 June 1
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 21, 1991 September 13
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 23, 1991 September 17
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 24, 1991 September 24
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 25, 1991 September 27
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 26, 1991 October 1
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 27, 1991 October 4
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 28, 1991 October 8
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 27, 1991 October 11
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 28, 1991 October 15
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 29, 1991 October 18
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 30, 1991 October 22
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 31, 1991 October 25
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 32, 1991 November 1
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 33, 1991 November 5
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 37, 1991 November 8
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 38, 1991 November 12
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 39, 1991 November 15
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 40, 1991 November 19
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 41, 1991 November 22
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 42, 1991 November 26
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 43, 1991 December 6
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 44, 1991 December 10
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 78, Number 46, 1991 December 13
  - Albany Student Press, 1992; 3
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 1, 1992 January 28
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 2, 1992 January 31
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 3, 1992 February 4
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 4, 1992 February 7
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 5, 1992 February 11
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 6, 1992 February 14
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 7, 1992 February 21
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 8, 1992 February 25
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 9, 1992 February 28
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 10, 1992 March 3
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 11, 1992 March 6
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 13, 1992 March 13
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 14, 1992 March 17
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 15, 1992 March 20
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 16, 1992 April 3
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 17, 1992 April 7
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 18, Special SA Endorsement Supplement, 1992 April 10
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 19, 1992 April 14
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 20, 1992 April 24
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 21, 1992 April 28
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 22, 1992 May 1
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 23, Summer Issue, 1992 Summer
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 24, 1992 September 11
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 25, 1992 September 15
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 27, 1992 September 22
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 28, 1992 October 2
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 29, 1992 October 13
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 30, 1992 October 16
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 31, 1992 October 20
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 32, 1992 October 23
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 33, 1992 October 27
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 34, 1992 October 30
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 35, 1992 November 3
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 36, 1992 November 6
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 38, 1992 November 17
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 39, 1992 November 20
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 40, 1992 November 24
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 41, 1992 December 4
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 42, 1992 December 8
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 43, 1992 December 11
  - Albany Student Press, 1993
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 1, 1993 January 26
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 2, 1993 January 26
    - Albany Student Press, Spring Edition, 1993 Spring
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 3, 1993 February 2
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 4, 1993 February 5
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 5, 1993 February 9
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 6, 1993 February 12
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 7, 1993 February 16
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 8, 1993 February 26
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 9, 1993 March 2
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 10, 1993 March 5
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 11, 1993 March 9
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 12, 1993 March 12
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 79, Number 13, 1993 March 19
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 80, Number 14, 1993 March 23
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 80, Number 15, 1993 March 26
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 80, Number 16, 1993 March 30
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 80, Number 17, 1993 April 16
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 80, Number 18, 1993 April 20
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 80, Number 19, 1993 April 23
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 80, Number 20, 1993 April 27
    - Albany Student Press, Volume 80, Number 21, 1993 April 30
- Albany Student Press, 2010s, 2014-2018; 10; 24 Digital Files
  - Albany Student Press, 2014-2015, 2 Digital Files
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 21, 2015 April 28; 12.00 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 22, 2015 May 5; 37.60 MB
  - Albany Student Press, 2015-2016, 22 Digital Files
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 1, 2015 September 1; 2.49 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 2, 2015 September 8; 15.50 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 3, 2015 September 22; 3.1 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 4, 2015 September 29; 2.8 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 5, 2015 October 6; 2.44 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 6, 2015 October 13; 3.08 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 7, 2015 October 20; 3.47 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 8, 2015 November 3; 3.16 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 9, 2015 November 10; 2.4 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 10, 2015 November 17; 3.6 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 11, 2015 November 24
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 12, 2015 December 8; 3.48 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 13, 2016 January 26; 2.62 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 14, 2016 February 2; 2.55 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 15, 2016 February 9; 3.02 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 16, 2016 February 16; 2.82 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 17, 2016 February 23; 2.34 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 18, 2016 March 1; 3.45 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 19, 2016 March 8; 3.02 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 20, 2016 April 5; 3.98 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 21, 2016 March 8
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 22, 2016 April 19; 3.41 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 23, 2016 April 26; 5.42 MB
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 24, 2016 May 3; 5.09 MB
  - Albany Student Press, 2016-2017, 19 Digital Files
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 1, 2016 September 6
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 2, 2016 September 13
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 3, 2016 September 20
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 4, 2016 September 27
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 5, 2016 October 4
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 6, 2016 October 18
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 7, 2016 October 25
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 8, 2016 November 1
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 9, 2016 November 8
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 10, 2016 November 15
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 10, 2016 December 6
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 1, 2017 January 31
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 2, 2017 February 7
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 3, 2017 February 14
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 4, 2017 February 21
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 5, 2017 February 28
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 6, 2017 March 7
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 7, 2017 March 28
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 8, 2017 April 4
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 9, 2017 April 25
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 10, 2017 May 2
  - Albany Student Press, 2017-2018, 20 Digital Files
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 1, 2017 September 5
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 2, 2017 September 12
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 3, 2017 September 19
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 4, 2017 October 3
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 5, 2017 October 24
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 6, 2017 October 31
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 7, 2017 November 7
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 8, 2017 November 14
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 9, 2017 November 21
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 10, 2017 December 5
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 1, 2018 January 30
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 2, 2018 February 6
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 3, 2018 February 13
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 4, 2018 February 27
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 5, 2018 March 6
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 6, 2018 March 27
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 7, 2018 April 10
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 8, 2018 April 17
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 9, 2018 April 24
    - Albany Student Press, Issue 10, 2018 May 1
  - Albany Student Press, 2018-2019
    - Albany Student Press, Fall Issue 1, 2018 September 4
    - Albany Student Press, Fall Issue 2, 2018 September 11
    - Albany Student Press, Fall Issue 3, 2018 September 18
    - Albany Student Press, Fall Issue 4, 2018 October 2
    - Albany Student Press, Fall Issue 5, 2018 October 9
    - Albany Student Press, Fall Issue 6, 2018 October 23
    - Albany Student Press, Fall Issue 7, 2018 October 30
    - Albany Student Press, Fall Issue 8, 2018 November 6
    - Albany Student Press, Fall Issue 9, 2018 November 13
    - Albany Student Press, Fall Issue 10, 2018 December 4
    - Albany Student Press, Spring Issue 1, 2019 February 5
    - Albany Student Press, Spring Issue 2, 2019 February 12
    - Albany Student Press, Spring Issue 3, 2019 February 19
    - Albany Student Press, Spring Issue 4, 2019 February 26
    - Albany Student Press, Spring Issue 5, 2019 March 5
    - Albany Student Press, Spring Issue 6, 2019 March 12
    - Albany Student Press, Spring Issue 7, 2019 April 2
    - Albany Student Press, Spring Issue 8, 2019 April 9
    - Albany Student Press, Spring Issue 9, 2019 April 16
    - Albany Student Press, Spring Issue 10, 2019 April 30
- Albany Student Press Website, 2013 February 15 - 2017 June 1; 11; 326 captures
  URL
  http://www.albanystudentpress.net/
  Access Requirements
  The item contains web archives preserved as WARC files. They must be access though web archival replay tools such as the "Wayback Machine." The links here direct you to files hosted by the Internet Archive, but you may also request WARC files.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service.
  This item is a seed within the Albany Student Press collection.
  Other seeds in this collection include: https://twitter.com/albstudentpress/
  Archive-it Collection Details:
  created_date: 2015-10-05T14:06:33Z
  created_by: gwiedeman
  state: ACTIVE
  last_updated_date: 2016-09-26T23:38:47Z
  last_updated_by: system
  Web Collection
  - The Albany Student Press |, 2013 February 15
    Scope and Contents
    Meta tag for description: Apple's search technology lawsuit against Samsung may go on hold - All you could want in a computer: The Lenovo IdeaCentre B540 - Big hedge funds fueled fourth-quarter dive in Apple shares -
    This crawl was performed by the Internet Archive, not the UAlbany web archiving program, so the provenance is unknown.
  - The Albany Student Press | Keeping UAlbany In The Spotlight, 2013 July 18
  - The Albany Student Press | Keeping UAlbany In The Spotlight, 2013 July 19
  - The Albany Student Press | Keeping UAlbany In The Spotlight, 2013 August 2
  - The Albany Student Press | Keeping UAlbany In The Spotlight, 2013 August 21
  - The Albany Student Press | Keeping UAlbany In The Spotlight, 2013 September 17
  - The Albany Student Press | Keeping UAlbany In The Spotlight, 2014 March 28
  - The Albany Student Press | Independent, Student-run weekly newspaper serving UAlbany, 2014 April 29
  - The Albany Student Press | Independent, Student-run weekly newspaper serving UAlbany, 2014 September 28
  - The Albany Student Press | Independent, Student-run weekly newspaper serving UAlbany, 2014 December 12
  - The Albany Student Press | Independent, Student-run weekly newspaper serving UAlbany, 2014 December 23
  - The Albany Student Press | Independent, Student-run weekly newspaper serving UAlbany, 2015 January 31
  - The Albany Student Press | Independent, Student-run weekly newspaper serving UAlbany, 2015 February 13
  - The Albany Student Press | Independent, Student-run weekly newspaper serving UAlbany, 2015 March 3
  - The Albany Student Press | Independent, Student-run weekly newspaper serving UAlbany, 2015 March 3
  - The Albany Student Press | Independent, Student-run weekly newspaper serving UAlbany, 2015 March 16
  - The Albany Student Press | Independent, Student-run weekly newspaper serving UAlbany, 2015 April 3
  - The Albany Student Press | Independent, Student-run weekly newspaper serving UAlbany, 2015 April 24
  - The Albany Student Press | Independent, Student-run weekly newspaper serving UAlbany, 2015 May 4
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 August 4
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 September 4
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 October 5
    Meta tag for description: UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 October 7
    crawl: 177302
    This item had no crawl rules.
    Crawl Times
    start_date: 2015-10-07T13:56:24Z
    original_start_date: 2015-10-07T13:56:24Z
    last_resumption: None
    processing_end_date: 2015-10-10T14:09:11Z
    end_date: 2015-10-10T13:56:49Z
    elapsed_ms: 259217556
    Crawl Types
    type: WEEKLY
    recurrence_type: WEEKLY
    pdfs_only: False
    test: False
    Crawl Limits
    time_limit: 259200
    document_limit: None
    byte_limit: None
    crawl_stop_requested: None
    Crawl Results
    status: FINISHED_TIME_LIMIT
    discovered_count: 144056
    novel_count: 102850
    duplicate_count: 31406
    resumption_count: 0
    queued_count: 9800
    downloaded_count: 134256
    download_failures: 2
    warc_revisit_count: 31406
    warc_url_count: 134212
    total_data_in_kbs: 4963419
    duplicate_bytes: 624902405
    warc_compressed_bytes: 727473145
    Crawl Technical Details
    doc_rate: 0.52
    kb_rate: 19.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 October 7
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Researchers interested in data analysis with web archives may request a WARC file. WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in advanced research with web archives.
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 October 7
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 October 7
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 October 14
    crawl: 178368
    start_date: 2015-10-14T13:56:36Z
    original_start_date: 2015-10-14T13:56:36Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-10-16T16:41:12Z
    end_date: 2015-10-16T16:20:01Z
    elapsed_ms: 181397230
    status: FINISHED
    discovered_count: 169219
    novel_count: 137278
    duplicate_count: 31941
    queued_count: 0
    downloaded_count: 169219
    download_failures: 4
    warc_revisit_count: 31940
    warc_url_count: 169179
    total_data_in_kbs: 6069741
    duplicate_bytes: 1018873368
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1572135306
    doc_rate: 0.93
    kb_rate: 33.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 October 14
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 October 21
    crawl: 179589
    start_date: 2015-10-21T13:56:33Z
    original_start_date: 2015-10-21T13:56:33Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-10-22T18:54:42Z
    end_date: 2015-10-22T18:16:14Z
    elapsed_ms: 101963379
    discovered_count: 134046
    novel_count: 117995
    duplicate_count: 16051
    downloaded_count: 134046
    warc_revisit_count: 16051
    warc_url_count: 134016
    total_data_in_kbs: 4337393
    duplicate_bytes: 691130338
    warc_compressed_bytes: 150580042
    doc_rate: 1.31
    kb_rate: 42.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 October 21
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 October 28
    crawl: 180671
    start_date: 2015-10-28T13:58:38Z
    original_start_date: 2015-10-28T13:58:38Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-10-29T19:10:52Z
    end_date: 2015-10-29T18:55:24Z
    elapsed_ms: 104191912
    discovered_count: 140633
    novel_count: 122391
    duplicate_count: 18242
    downloaded_count: 140633
    warc_revisit_count: 18242
    warc_url_count: 140598
    total_data_in_kbs: 5291825
    duplicate_bytes: 726732476
    warc_compressed_bytes: 358169677
    doc_rate: 1.35
    kb_rate: 50.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 October 28
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 November 4
    crawl: 181746
    start_date: 2015-11-04T13:56:35Z
    original_start_date: 2015-11-04T13:56:35Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-11-05T21:54:55Z
    end_date: 2015-11-05T21:14:31Z
    elapsed_ms: 112661692
    discovered_count: 120114
    novel_count: 104858
    duplicate_count: 15256
    downloaded_count: 120114
    warc_revisit_count: 15256
    warc_url_count: 120079
    total_data_in_kbs: 4117337
    duplicate_bytes: 510325541
    warc_compressed_bytes: 258252133
    doc_rate: 1.07
    kb_rate: 36.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 November 4
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 November 7
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 November 11
    crawl: 182784
    start_date: 2015-11-11T13:56:39Z
    original_start_date: 2015-11-11T13:56:39Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-11-12T22:27:46Z
    end_date: 2015-11-12T22:07:21Z
    elapsed_ms: 115835024
    discovered_count: 144081
    novel_count: 127672
    duplicate_count: 16409
    downloaded_count: 144081
    warc_revisit_count: 16409
    warc_url_count: 144043
    total_data_in_kbs: 5394790
    duplicate_bytes: 740561901
    warc_compressed_bytes: 397123346
    doc_rate: 1.24
    kb_rate: 46.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 November 11
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 November 18
    crawl: 183822
    start_date: 2015-11-18T13:56:30Z
    original_start_date: 2015-11-18T13:56:30Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-11-19T21:55:13Z
    end_date: 2015-11-19T21:26:44Z
    elapsed_ms: 113406298
    discovered_count: 142771
    novel_count: 126428
    duplicate_count: 16343
    downloaded_count: 142771
    warc_revisit_count: 16343
    warc_url_count: 142733
    total_data_in_kbs: 5396545
    duplicate_bytes: 760921378
    warc_compressed_bytes: 387263384
    doc_rate: 1.26
    kb_rate: 47.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 November 18
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 November 25
    crawl: 184865
    start_date: 2015-11-25T13:56:29Z
    original_start_date: 2015-11-25T13:56:29Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-11-26T23:02:40Z
    end_date: 2015-11-26T22:34:52Z
    elapsed_ms: 117495502
    discovered_count: 143781
    novel_count: 128725
    duplicate_count: 15056
    downloaded_count: 143781
    warc_revisit_count: 15056
    warc_url_count: 143744
    total_data_in_kbs: 5802462
    duplicate_bytes: 622803798
    warc_compressed_bytes: 834581316
    doc_rate: 1.22
    kb_rate: 49.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 November 25
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 December 2
    crawl: 185748
    start_date: 2015-12-02T13:56:32Z
    original_start_date: 2015-12-02T13:56:32Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-12-04T01:32:06Z
    end_date: 2015-12-04T00:53:16Z
    elapsed_ms: 125795156
    discovered_count: 144241
    novel_count: 128763
    duplicate_count: 15478
    downloaded_count: 144241
    warc_revisit_count: 15478
    warc_url_count: 144207
    total_data_in_kbs: 5836318
    duplicate_bytes: 1061923018
    warc_compressed_bytes: 415413618
    doc_rate: 1.15
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 December 2
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 December 9
  - Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 December 9
    crawl: 186690
    start_date: 2015-12-09T13:56:31Z
    original_start_date: 2015-12-09T13:56:31Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-12-12T14:10:48Z
    end_date: 2015-12-12T13:56:58Z
    elapsed_ms: 259217119
    discovered_count: 172186
    novel_count: 159362
    duplicate_count: 12751
    queued_count: 73
    downloaded_count: 172113
    warc_revisit_count: 12750
    warc_url_count: 172061
    total_data_in_kbs: 6373386
    duplicate_bytes: 995652782
    warc_compressed_bytes: 716596286
    doc_rate: 0.66
    kb_rate: 24.0